# Ming Shun Kwek

Software Student

Currently a year 3 computer engineering student studying at National University of Singapore. Clear communicator and determine in tasks I set my mind too. Forward-thinking development professional bringing expertise in Java, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and other programming languages. Diligently learning everything I can, gaining more experience in different fields so that one day, I could contribute more towards the world of technology.

# **Work History**

#### Java Software Developer 2021-06 -2022-02

Integro Technologies Pte Ltd

- Troubleshot various software issues by using debugging processes and coding techniques.
- Investigated issues and defects to determine problem root cause and formulate corrective action recommendations, successfully resolving over 30 issues.
- Wrote, modified and maintained software documentation and specifications.

## 2019-11 -2020-08

## **Head of Programmes**

NUS Raffles Hall Freshmen Orientation Camp

- Coordinated sequence of programmes for 200 freshmen, while maintaining communication across multiple departments to ensure smooth operation while clarifying conflicting ideas.
- Spearheading team of 10, like-minded individuals while resolve conflicting visions, guiding innovation towards enhancing event flow.

### 2020-05 -2020-07

## **Software Development**

NUS Orbital Programme

 Developed SmartTrack savings application in React Native that aids in budget management with additional features that ease expense sharing with

### Contact

#### Address

Singapore, Singapore

#### Phone

(+65) 8125 9299

#### E-mail

mingshun1998@hotmail.co m

#### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/kwekming-shun

#### **GitHub**

github.com/MingShun98

#### **Personal Website**

mingshun98.github.io/Portf olio-Website/

## Skills

Object-Oriented Programming



Effective Communication for Computing Professionals



Data Structures and Algorithms



Code versioning



\_

other users.

 Achieved Apollo 11 (advanced) standard certification, determined to have demonstrated awareness of basics in software engineering, testing and documentation.

 Picked up relevant software development skills and knowledge like Javascript and Google Firebase API.

# 2018-11 - Contracts/Projects Assistant

YL Integrated PTE LTD

- Analyzed and calculated required lighting and fire emergency equipment in floor plans for tender projects, necessary for purchase and installation.
- Managed contact between suppliers and company, answering inquires regarding quotations as well as purchase orders.
- Managed and mentored team of 3 employees, overseeing training, and professional growth of employees.

# 2017-08 - Sergeant, 1st Battalion Singapore Guards 2018-11 Singapore Armod Forces (National Service)

Singapore Armed Forces (National Service)

- Planned for mission objectives and engaging in discussions with full time servicemen to better optimized battle plans and efficient routes for mission success.
- Facilitated 30+ recruits as an instructor, teaching and mentoring enlistees, later transitioned into leader role after recruits graduated from Basic Training and thereafter, being responsible for them during active service.

# **Education**

2019-06

## 2019-08 - Bachelor of Engineering: Computer Engineering

**Current** National University of Singapore

• GPA: 4.05/5.00

# 2015-01 - High School Diploma 2016-12

Nanyang Junior College

 Achieved 78.75 RP with 2 H2 Distinctions in Chemistry and Mathematics. Functional Specification documentation

Very Good

Very Good

Mobile/ Web Development



# Languages

English



Mandarin Chinese



## Software

Java Programming



C++ Programming



HTML/ CSS / JavaScript



C Programming



Git/ Github



Python



SQL

